Rahul Chandel

Java Backend Developer



□ rahulchandel2824@gmail.com

in rahul-chandel-16323619b

RahulChandel-Coder1

Skills

JAVA • Spring Boot • Hibernate • SQL

HTML • CSS • JavaScript

Data Structure & Algorithm

Soft Skills - (Problem Solving, Strong Work Ethic Java, Self-Motivation, Always Ready to learn new things)

Education

Boot Camp, Masai School

03/2022 - 09/2022

MCA, Graphic Era University

08/2019 - 07/2021 | Dehradun, Uttrakhand

BCA, Beehive Group College

08/2016 - 07/2019 | Dehradun, Uttarakhand

Higher Secondary, Indian Public School

04/2015 - 03/2016 | Dehradun

Certificates

Core Java (NPTL-2019), ADSE(Advance Diploma in software **Engineering)** (07/2017-12/2018)

Profile

Skilled Backend Developer and Computer Science post graduate with proficiency in Java. Problem Solving mindset and quick learner who possesses the ability to adapt to new environments quickly. Looking challenging role in the industry to utilize my skill and learning.

Projects

ZEE5, OTT platform website

06/2022 - 06/2022

- I have done this website individually.
- Develop Navbar, Home page, Product page.
- Using Filter functionality Login/Signup page.

Tech Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

Dermstore Clone. E-commerce Website for skincare Products

05/2022 - 05/2022

- Navbar with different pages.
- Product page has sort Functionality.
- I worked on Home page and different Product pages.
- Developed along with a team of 4 members in one weak.

Online Learning Platform, learning app

01/2021 - 05/2022

- Develop Teacher Section in this application.
- Separate login/signup for teacher's.
- Get notifications when ever new student join.

Tech Stack: Python & Django, HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

Professional Experience

MultiGraphics pvt. ltd., IT-Executive

08/2021 - 02/2022 | Dehradun

- Work on MIS software.
- Provide network support in company.
- Provide training to new Employees about Work Flow of MIS software.

Internship

01/2021 - 05/2021 | Indore, India

- Work in a Team learn new Technologies.
- Work on a Live Project Online Learning Platform.